ifpma.org 2015-03-14

# Privacy Policy : IFPMA

The IFPMA is committed to protecting the privacy and security of visitors to our website. Outlined below is our online privacy policy for information collected through our website. If you have questions about these policies, please feel free to contact us at admin@ifpma.org. 

Normal Website usage  
In General, you can browse the IFPMA site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. 

Personal Information  
Should you be asked to provide personal information such as your name, e-mail contact and postal address when requesting information, giving feedback, register to a newsletter, or any other functions of the website, be assured that all such information is considered by IFPMA both private and secure. The IFPMA does not share or sell personal information it has gathered about you to third parties. Under no circumstance will details be disclosed publicly, except in order to comply with any legal obligation. This policy reiterates that IFPMA fully appreciates the importance of feeling safe online and is committed to protecting your personal information.

To enable IFPMA to process any order or registration to an event, IFPMA may use a secure online payment facility which is enabled to process payments using credit card details. This facility is run by a third party organization and IFPMA will not be collecting or storing credit card details on our IT systems.

Please be aware that other websites to which we link, including social media, may collect personally identifiable information about you when you visit those sites. The information practices of other websites linked to our site are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

Browser information collected on our website  
We analyze our website logs to constantly improve the value of our website. We do not use this analysis to gather, request, record or track any internet users’ personally identifiable information. 

Cookies and IP addresses  
We use cookies on our site to personalize and customize the experience of our visitors and to support some necessary functions. We also use cookie to better understand how our visitors use our site. You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. However, please note that if you reject some or all cookies, your experience at this and other sites throughout the Internet may not be complete.  
The IFPMA may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

DISCLAIMER

Information included  
The material contained on this web site is for information only. IFPMA endeavours to make its best effort to up-date the information on a regular basis, but it is not claimed to be exhaustive. This information is believed to be correct. Nevertheless, IFPMA makes no representations or warranties as to the completeness or accuracy of any of this information. IFPMA will in no event be responsible for damages of any nature whatsoever resulting from the use of or reliance on the information contained in this web site. 

Links  
Links to other web sites are provided solely as a convenience. Therefore, those links imply neither responsibility for, nor approval of, the information contained in these web sites by IFPMA.
